

Kamil Kawałkiewicz kamil.kawalkiewicz@gmail.com 661182004 https://github.com/ KamilKawalkiewicz

address: Kraków

portfolio: https://kamilkawalkiewicz. github.io/Portfolio/

Kamil Kawałkiewicz

About me

Since 2018 I have been acquiring technical skills to work as a Front-end Developer. During this time I have completed some interesting projects which You can see in my portfolio. My primary skills are HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React.js. I'm familiar with Git for source control and I'm also further developing my skills in Front-end by learning SASS and BEM.

SKILLS

Coding

• HTML (BEM) • CSS Wordpress • SASS • React.js • PrestaShop • Java-Script o PHP

Bootstrap MySQLSQL

Programming tools

Webpack • GIT NPM

Language

• English - B1

EXPERIENCE

10.2019 - 02.2020 Frontend Developer at CASHCROWN.PL

Responsibilities:

- Déveloping websites
- Solving basic SEO issuesCreating website templates for SEO
- Auditing and optimising websites
- Creating advertisement services in Wordpress
- Building e-commerce stores in PrestaShopUsing FTP servers
- Used technologies and tools: HTML, CSS, SCSS, JS, WebPack, NPM, Git, Web.dev, Gtmetrix, Website Auditor, Wordpress, PrestaShop, cPanel and FileZilla.

2018- 2019 Spa sanatorium "Dedal"

Responsibilities:

performing treatments in the field of physiotherapy

Skills acquired:

- good communication and team work
- problem solving and compromise
- working in high pressure environment and coping with stress
- kindness and positive attitude towards people

EDUCATION

2011-2013 Academy of Physical Education in Wrocław Master in Physiotherapy

2007-2010 State Higher School in Tarnów Bachelor in Physiotherapy